Today, I'm going to be backtesting 1
month worth of data using my 70% win
rate strategy. You guys are going to see
real time how I go about determining my
bias on the higher time frame to then
executing my model on the lower time.
So, let's get into it. All right, first
things first, I'm going to ask my phone
to give me a random day, month, and
year. Hey Siri, can you give me a random
day, month, and year in between the
years 2020 to 2025? Okay. Okay, August
14th of 2023.
2023, let's run it up. That's in the
summer. We can work with that. today
we're going to be backtesting using
TradeZella. So, TradeZella is a
journaling software, but as well, it is
a backtesting software. So, you can
backtest with it as well, and I'm super
hyped to use this. Let's just click
start backtesting. We're going to click
create our own strategy. Our strategy
name is the MECH Model. Description,
we'll just put 70% win rate strat. We
can put a little icon too. I'll put the
little ninja emoji there. So, we'll have
an entry criteria. So, for me to take a
trade, I need price to be bouncing off
of a higher time frame key level. I also
need there to be an obvious draw on
liquidity and for price to be aligned
with the higher time frame trend. And
then finally, I will put
displacement/confirmation
with an IFEG. All right, so these are
all my rules for my model, and now let's
click save and back. And now we can head
over to strategies. We can click the
MECH Model. You can click backtesting,
and we will click create backtesting
session. So, the session name, I'll just
put YouTube vid. Strategy, I'll just put
MECH Model. Symbols, we'll do NQ and ES
futures. Start date is August 14th of
2023,
and then end date we'll do September
14th of 2023. Cool. And we'll do a
starting balance, we'll just do like a
50K account. And now let's create the
session, maybe. Chart colors are
absolutely hideous, so let me change
these really quick. 3 2 1. All right,
there we go. Now we have our chart
colors all ready. This is beautiful. All
right, so let's do a session. Let's just
do 1 month worth of data. I typically
don't recommend you guys to be
backtesting 1 month worth of data. I do
think that's a little bit OD, but just
for the sake of this video, I do want to
do a large set of data. I don't just
want to do one week. But, I recommend
everyone to do at least one week worth
of data every single day. And you can do
this using TradeZella, best journaling
software and backtesting software in the
game right now. They're coming out with
a bunch of new features with that. So,
link's in the description if you guys
want to sign up with TradeZella. So,
starting on the higher higher time
frame, first off, let's just go to New
York session. So, start of New York
session around like 9:50, okay. So, draw
on liquidity and bias. All right, so
hourly time frame, we do have this
bullish SMT in place right now with this
low here on ES and then this right here.
So, we could see price bouncing off
here. The only thing I'm not liking
right now is how we are respecting this
bearish gap right here and then we are
disrespecting this bullish gap right
here. So, we're respecting bearish,
disrespecting bullish, meaning we are
probably going to go to this low. Now,
this low could also be a protected low.
Say price just starts displacing higher,
then we could look for some potential
longs, but yeah, I mean I'm going to be
leaning more bearish because of that.
So, let's see what 9:30 wants to do
here. Play out 9:30 open, 3 2 1. This is
open, so 9:30 ended up trading lower
here. Not really loving anything at the
moment. Looks like we're just kind of
bearish towards this low, but we do have
some nice trend line here. Maybe we run
that. I'd like to see price go up
towards this 15-minute intermediate high
right now. Okay. So, boom, we got that.
A short off this could be good, right?
We have this low intact. an hourly
inverse to the downside. So, if this
wants to be bearish, what should we do
with this 15-minute intermediate high?
We should respect this and then trade
lower. Now, what do we also have in this
range? A 5-minute gap. This is a great
condition to have because if we are
going to be bullish, this will get
respected, we will get some sort of
inversion to the upside, and then we
will just be bullish. But, if this wants
to get disrespected, then we can be
bearish and take some sort of short.
That's why I really like 5-minute gaps
as conditions. So, let's see, we trade
back to that. Okay, and if we get some
sort of 5-minute inverse to the
downside, I will be willing to take a
short. But, as well as like I'm not
really too opposed to longs just cuz I
can see the narrative for it being that
we are looking like this could be a
protected low with this SMT. So, let's
see. All right, yeah, we got that
inversion to the upside. Unfortunately,
no entry on that, but we are just going
to go higher. There's no entry because
we did take out the internal high. We
can just keep playing out price here.
Could get a short opportunity maybe if
we get a 2-minute inverse. I'm not
really loving shorts right now, though.
The reason I'm not loving shorts is
because we're just displacing through
this 15-minute immediate high, leading
me to want to be a little bit more
bullish towards these accumulation zone
highs. If we were going to be bearish
here, this should have just been an
immediate soup and we should have gone
lower, but we're not doing that. We're
respecting bullish gaps now, so. So,
nothing really that I love yet. Just got
to keep playing out price here. All
right, so we're getting really close to
this high right here, these accumulation
zone highs. Maybe some sort of 5-minute
pullback, maybe a 30-second, not just a
little bit too choppy. It's probably
going to be a no entry on this. Yeah, no
entry. Go back lower now. There is this
long here, right? We are rejecting off
of this 5-minute fair value gap.
Honestly, I do like this for a long,
just a continuation model. Rejecting off
this 5-minute gap, and we can just look
to target this high right here. Looking
just a lot more bullish here, right? ES
still has to run these highs, so I'm
actually put on some indicators. I'm
going to put on the sessions indicators,
which reads out. Let's see. All right,
so I mean, this is going to be a pretty
scuffed entry, but I will try this just
because the break even point is so
obvious. We can put a stop loss like
here. We can put a stop loss here.
I'm going to put a TP up here. Just go
for about a 1:1. I just really like this
being an obvious break even point.
Clearly trending up here, bouncing off
the 5-minute gap. Really textbook setup.
I don't expect price to go back to this
unfilled 15-minute gap yet because this
is a breakaway gap because we did just
trade into that with the 5-minute, so.
I'm going to try this long. This will be
the first trade. We can do 490 risk. All
right, cool. So, we'll go for about a
one to one RR here. Also, the candle
didn't even close actually. Oh, but
there was a two-minute close. Was there
a two-minute close? Sorry, guys. I'm
still kind of getting used to this. Oh,
I didn't sync the time frame. Oh, but
there was a close right here. Honestly,
this is not a trade I would take if I'm
just being completely honest. So, I'm
just being honest, guys. This wouldn't
be a trade I would take because I don't
like this initial close and then the
close is actually up here. So, even
though this was a winning trade, I don't
want to be like faking the stats here.
That's just probably not a trade I would
take um
just because the close. But, yeah. I
mean, obvious bias after that. Like, I
mean, I was leaning more bearish just
because of that, but we obviously have
conditions and the conditions did not
the conditions did not confirm anything.
So, that being said, let's just move on
to Tuesday. So far, zero trades on the
week, but bias. Hopefully, you guys are
learning something from that at least,
of course.
Okay. So, hourly time frame. What are we
doing? We are displacing from this low
and we also have this high. ES is
looking a lot more bearish. Okay, the
four-hour time frame on ES is all the
way down here. Right? So, we're probably
going for these lows on ES.
>> [music]
>> I'm leaning a little bit more bearish
just because of ES. We're kind of
bouncing in between these two PD arrays,
but I want to see NQ do some sort of
open high into that hourly intermediate
high and then get some sort of short out
of there. That would be nice. Or, if we
start displacing through that. Okay, so
we already hit this high pre-market.
Let's see if we want to go and run that
high again. We do. Nothing really yet
that I love. Probably a little 30-second
here. Honestly, do really like this. I
will try this 30-second. We have an
unfilled five-minute gap right here.
30-second. How much do I like this
30-second is the real question. The
thing is it is a little bit choppy.
Honestly, yeah. I don't really love this
because we did just trade into this
15-minute gap actually. So, we literally
just traded into this 15-minute gap. I
will personally be fading this. I think
this is not a bad play, but I want to
see a little bit more confirmation. Then
maybe like a five-minute continuation, a
15-minute continuation, then we can
target this low. As of now, just for the
plain fact that we already hit that
15-minute gap, that would be a point
where I'd want to go break even. So, I'm
just going to fade this initial short.
Looks like it fails, and then we get
this here. Yeah, it's just a little
choppy right now. Okay, so here's what I
want. Yep, we're displacing now. This
SMT is holding, right? We have a bearish
SMT in play. [music] Displacing lower
here. We're opening up a 5-minute gap,
looks like. Trade still is a little bit
laggy. All right, so we have a 5-minute
gap here. Uh there's a 30-second
inverse. This 30-second looks really
nice. Yeah, bouncing off a 5-minute gap.
We have clear lows down here. We are
inverting. Yeah, this looks actually
super textbook if we can hold this
5-minute gap. Okay, so I mean,
diabolical close there, but I still will
take this and just put a stop at like
this displacing candle. Or we can put it
at just like this high. That's good. And
go for about a 1:1.3 RR towards this
low. So, I really like this. Again,
respecting this bearish gap, respecting
this bearish gap up here. We have a
bearish SMT. ES is more bearish on the
higher time frame. Um so, just alongside
that trend. I don't really see a point
to go break even here at this low just
because I don't know. I mean, there's
there's just no reason to go break even
at this low. I would rather go break
even maybe when we get closer. I have a
lot of confidence in this trade, so I
don't really think this is like a valid
reason to go break even. A lot of people
ask me like, "Where do you go break
even?" Like, and it really depends every
single time. Like, usually it's at the
internal lower high. Other times, it
could be if I have a lot of conviction
in the trade and this intermediate lower
high or this internal lower high is not
a point in which I think price could
reverse from, then I'm not willing to go
break even at that point, right? So, I'm
going to try to enter shorts here. We'll
get it with one con.
And we'll do
one contract here, so
Okay, cool. Risking about 535 to make
700, so
let's play this out. Rejecting this
30-second bearish gap here, which is
exactly what I want to see. Nice, still
respecting it, trading lower, respecting
that gap. Right, so the reason also see
why I didn't go break even here because
we hit this, we go back to this
30-second gap to send price lower. Now,
I see this area as protected. I don't
want to see price trade back to this
area. So, now I will go break even and
super close to TP here. This 1-minute
gap should send price lower
for this 30 second. There we go.
Beautiful. Really, really nice there.
Got about a 1:1.3 RR on that trade. So,
really happy with that. Very textbook
setup here. Super textbook continuation
and this just absolutely dumps. But,
giving me a nice 1:1, getting my piece
of the pie and I'm out there. All right,
let's go to the next day. All right, I'm
going to try to make this video like
informative while at the same time not
being super slow with every single day.
I'm just going to show you guys like how
I backtest like normally. Yeah, okay. We
are really bearish obviously. We are
just dumping right now. So, I'd want to
see some sort of short here. Uh, maybe
price trades up to this 15-minute
bearish gap to send price lower. Could
get something like that. That would be
nice. And 30 opens, we go lower. Okay.
Now, we're going higher to this
15-minute gap. I'm chopping around.
Little MD. You have an hourly gap up
here. This could be the high of day. I
do like this. See if we want to soup
that or go lower. So, right now like
internally, right? There we are setting
up for some sort of short. Yeah, so this
is going to be a short. I don't love
this. Why don't I love this? Because we
didn't hit any key level, right? We're
rejecting off this, but the key level I
really want to see is that 1-hour
intermediate high or that 1-hour fair
value gap. To me, this is just
generating liquidity. So, if anything,
this is leaning a little bit more
bullish mechanically. 15-minute gap here
is going to open up. But, this will
probably play. This MACD model will
probably play out. Yeah, so it plays
out. This short works. Again, just not
something I'd I'm personally willing to
take just cuz we didn't hit that high.
But, longs here look great, right? Okay,
so I do like longs here. Little 1-minute
inverse. 2-minute. But, yeah, I mean
this 1-minute is all I need. This is a
lot of displacement up. Super, super
bullish reaction off of this. Yeah, I
for sure will be taking this. I'll just
try to aim for like a 1:1, stop at this
candle right here, and TP up there. I
mean, this is a super textbook setup,
right? We have an unfilled 15-minute gap
right here, MAC model. We are just
placing off of this bullish 15-minute
gap, and obvious equal highs up here.
I'll aim for that one to one. So, I'll
try this with 565. I can't do exact risk
because I'm on NQ. If I was on MNQ, I'd
be able to do exact risk, like risk 1%
perfectly every time. Okay, wait. I'm
still not at a one to one. One to one
would be up here. Okay, cool. Okay, I'm
definitely going to go break even there.
One point away. Bro, there's no way. I
was like one point away from my TP. But,
break even here, obviously, cuz we did
hit my target. I was just aiming for
that one to one.
Okay, there we go. I was going to say,
dude, super close to TP there, but yeah,
there's that one to one. That's why it's
kind of sketchy sometimes. Like, I could
have just moved my stop. There's times
where I move my stop, and I just like
put my TP for the one to one. There's
times where I just have my stop be the
same, and then ex- extend the TP.
There's really no like right way of
doing it, honestly. It's just wherever
like whatever the setup's showing you.
Like, if you can put your stop higher,
then put your stop higher. If you can't,
and I really only saw this as like the
best stop loss possible, then I'm just
going to put it there. All right, cool.
We'll move on. So far, two and 0 on the
week. Let's move on to the next step.
But, super simple. All right, let's talk
about bias now for this day. Let's
remove all the drawings. We are
obviously going to this weekly low. So,
very, very obviously going for this low
unless did ES take this out? [music] ES
did sweep out a daily low here. Could
see some sort of bullish reaction off of
that, but honestly, like I'm leaning a
lot more bearish. We have a lot of trend
line liquidity here as well. I'd want to
take some short entries. We also have a
data low here. So, leaning a little bit
more bearish. Let's see, 9:30 open high,
or we just take out the data low. Now,
for me to take a short, what do I need
to see? Man, was there 30 second in
this? Okay, but let's see. Still really
bearish here because we are respecting
this 15-minute gap right here. We have
all this trend line, and still the
weekly draws lower on NQ. Um so, I'm
still looking to see prices lower. See
if we want to get some sort of 5-minute
continuation. All right, 5-minute gap
here. So, if we tap that, we also have
an unfilled 5-minute gap as a DOL right
here. So, this looks actually super
nice. No, we were so close. Damn, super
close. No entry on that, unfortunate.
All right, we'll keep looking. All
right, another 5-minute gap tap here. I
mean, in a 1-minute. Dude, I honestly
just want to try this just because I
mean, this will most likely be a
break-even trade, but you don't know.
Sometimes you can get away with like
these type of trades and these just
flush. I mean, I'm not going to lie,
this is definitely going to be a
break-even trade either way, but really,
really obvious draw, right? 5-minute
continuation model. We are clearly
displacing lower. I say it's just worth
a shot, and I'll just probably aim for
this [music] low right here. Or just
because of how bad this entry is, bro,
I'm going to go for the one to one with
a stop at that the displacing candle's
high. I can honestly put it at the body.
Yeah, I don't want to see price going
higher than that. I mean, there's no way
we reverse all the way up back up there,
and yeah, okay. Let's rip this. I'm
going to go for two contracts like as
much as I can do. I can do about two
contracts for 670, a little bit more
than 1%, but okay, let's try this. This
will definitely be a break-even trade,
but let's just like make sure we're not
getting screwed here by going on 30
second. Okay, so break-even here. See,
this is an entry where I feel
comfortable going break-even this early.
And the reason I want to go break-even
this early is just because we are like
hitting all these draws. I could see
price rebalancing, could see price
dropping. This is just an entry where
the draw on the equity is still a little
bit far. So, yeah, break-even trade. No,
man, brutal, but we could get some sort
of
maybe re-entry. We still have the draw
intact, like we still have draws intact
here. [music] I mean, SMTs were forming,
dude. I'm just super confident in this
draw right now, which is why I'm just
looking for any entry. Oh, it's going to
hit. Man, it hits right there. Off of
like no key level, though. We still have
an unfilled 15-minute gap there. Yeah,
session's chopped. I mean, we're just
bearish as hell, going for this low. I
doubt I'm going to get an entry now.
Okay, yeah, just dumps with no entry.
We'll move on to the next day.
Unfortunate break even, but it is what
it is. Okay, so bias honestly inside of
this new week opening gap could see a
bounce off of that. Did ES hit anything?
We still have this low on ES. So could
be bearish towards that. Also do have
unfilled gaps up here. We have a lot of
trend line liquidity as well above us.
Could see a rebalance. Could see a
reversal. I'm open to anything honestly.
I'm I'm leaning a little bit more
bearish just because of this low on ES,
but let's see what we want to do with
open. So an open high low close here
would be A plus honestly.
9:30 give me an open high. Okay, okay,
okay, okay. See, I would never long this
just cuz look how close this low is on
ES. Way too close. Whoa. Look at this
move. Man, we're way too close to this
15 minute immediate high and it's an
unfilled hourly. Yeah, not a trade I'd
ever take. I want to see price generate
liquidity here. Give me one more swing
up. One more swing up. Okay. Honestly, I
really do like this short. A lot of
trend line liquidity here. I mean, we're
inside this hourly fair value gap. 15
minute immediate high sweep. Low
resistance liquidity. We have an
accumulation manipulation. We have an
inversion to the downside. ES is well
really close to the sell side here. I
would definitely be taking this short
here. I just need one more candle. This
is a two minute close. So I need to see
a two minute close below this. Okay, so
there's the entry. Damn, a little bit
worse of an entry, but it's all good.
Stop loss here. We'll just go for a one
to one. Honestly, you can put the stop
loss like a little bit tighter. Yeah.
Okay, I'm going to try this. Low
resistance liquidity. Two minute
inverse. We have an order block here
also to support price lower. I could put
my stop loss like even here, but just
because this gap is unmitigated probably
like wick into it if anything. All
right, so let's try this. Number of cons
max max risk percent two. All right, so
we're risking around $600 to make $600.
So around 1% or a little bit more than
1%. Let's try this though. I'm not going
to lie. I don't really see any point in
going break even now just cuz this is
low resistance liquidity. Maybe once we
take out this internal low now, I I go
break even. Okay, so now I'll go break
even. Now I think there's a good point
to go break even. Do not want to see
price go back up.
Beautiful. All right, and we're out
there. That's it. That's all I need. My
one-to-one and my piece of the pie.
Beautiful short here. Again, aligned
with that higher time frame trend. We're
just using that as a magnet and now I
don't care, right? We can go up, we can
go down, we can do whatever the [\h__\h] we
want. We want to chop around. Sure.
Cool. End to the week. All right, what
was that? Three and oh on the week.
Really solid start. Let's go to the next
week. Inside of this bearish daily gap,
bearish 4-hour gap as well. We have an
unmitigated 4-hour up here we could see,
but I am liking shorts. I'm liking
shorts more, honestly. All right. But
let's see what 9:30 wants to do. Maybe a
retrace. Yeah, I like shorts here.
Accumulation, manipulation. Maybe tap
into this and send price lower. See 9:30
opens higher and we just displace up,
actually. Okay. Well, we have the
unfilled 4-hour right here as a good
draw. Bouncing, obviously, off of this
1-hour gap. Really bullish move. Damn,
no entry for that. 5-minute tap. We're
going to have some sort of 30-second
There's a 30-second long right here.
What do we think about this? The only
reason I don't really like this is just
because we did just sweep or just did
tap into this 15-minute gap. I'd rather
see price like generate liquidity, have
this be another re-sweep, and then go
for a long. I'm not really loving longs
right here. Yeah, there we go. Because
again, we did just tap into this 4-hour,
so trying to long again to this high
immediately is like pretty low quality.
We have a 9:35 devil's mark here. So,
maybe make the candle on this and then
we could get some sort of reaction now
that we're just generating liquidity to
the downside or to the upside. Nope, we
don't get it. Damn, I really wanted
that. I wanted that discounted 5-minute
tap really bad. Brutal. Brutal. Do we do
it on ES? Nah. Yeah, I mean there's a
30-second long. It was okay. Dude, it's
just so choppy. See what we react off
this. Yeah, nothing I love yet. Maybe
honestly, maybe a 5-minute inverse
wouldn't be bad. It's not a close. So,
we are inside of a 15-minute gap, but
I'm not going to lie, I really do like I
don't know. We have another 5 minute
here. Or no, it's a 4 minute. Yeah, the
5 minute's closing. I honestly do really
like this short. I want to try this just
to the this right here. The only
problem, man, this is going to be tough.
Stop loss here. This is going to be like
a big trade. So, break even would be at
the unfilled 15-minute gap. I know we
are on side of another 5 minute, but
this is or another 15 minute, but this
is enough displacement for me to try
something like this. This is a 950 low.
We do have that SMC. I really do like
this 4-hour high here. Daily gap is just
getting respected. All right, let me try
this short. I'm willing to put on risk
for this. Number of cons I will do Oh,
wow, that's a lot. I can do it actually
at this order block at the 1-minute OB.
Damn, that's still risking 710. [music]
Okay, well, I'm willing to put on this
risk honestly. So, I'll try this. Risk
one con here. It's a lot of risk, but
I'm willing to do it. Bang. Beautiful.
Okay, break even here. Look at that
displacement. Beautiful. Like just look
at this soup on ES. Look at the
5-minute. It was just enough
displacement for me to try something
like this.
And bang. TP there. Look at that TP.
Beautiful.
Okay, super nice. Got myself that
one-to-one. All I needed I just needed
that little piece of the pie. All right,
we can move on now. This was Monday.
Great great start. We're actually
cooking right now. All right, Tuesday.
All right, Tuesday. So, leaning a lot
more bullish here. We're obviously just
disrespecting all these gaps in this
range. I just want to be on side this
trend honestly. We're just ripping
higher. So, that's really not trying to
That's really it. Just ripping higher.
Maybe a little paddy swing, little 93
Judas. Ooh, no paddy swing. We're
actually going a lower here. Okay, I
could see this going down to this
unfilled 15-minute gap. It's the most
obvious area of interest. So, maybe a
short down to here would be nice. Okay,
cuz we did also obviously sweep out this
like 4-hour [music]
intermediate high. This is also a daily
premium gap on ES. So, like this
reaction is completely valid. Maybe a
continuation model. Okay. Honestly, I am
willing to try this short. We have a
5-minute rebounds here. The 50-minute is
in the sell model, right? We're
disrespecting these gaps, delivering off
of this daily for rally gap, 4-hour new
high. I was super daily bullish coming
into the day, but I could see this
rebalance just because of how
overextended we are. Um so, I will try
this. Maybe to I mean, we also have this
unfilled 50-minute gap. This will be a
good draw. I'll try this. 30-second
short here. This was the highest time
frame in this manipulation leg. And we
can put a stop loss at this high, put a
TP down there. This is great
risk-to-reward as well. We can do one
con, risk 360, or try risk 720. See,
this is the problem with like trading on
NQ also versus MNQ. It's like that's
such a fat difference, [music] bro. All
right, whatever. I think I'll just rip
that 720 risk, honestly. We'll send it.
Big balls here. All right. I'll go break
even once we take out this low. Or
honestly, now that we traded into this
gap, and we took out this internal low,
I will go break even. I like this being
my break-even point now. Oh, so close. I
could just rip that one to one, but I
honestly have a lot of conviction this
unfilled 50-minute gap down here. So,
I'm going to hold for this. Again, this
30-second inverse continuation model.
What?
There's no way.
Bang! There we go. I was going to say,
dude. What an actual banger of a trade
there. Okay, beautiful. Look at that TP.
Beautiful. Let's move on now. All right,
we are Wait, bro. We are actually
cooking right now. Let's see. Unfilled
daily gap. We're just in between this
range right now. So, we have previous
day high right here, and previous day
low intact. So, what do I want to see? I
want to see I mean, I really like this
range. Just wherever we start displacing
to, I'll take either a long if we start
displacing higher, or a short if we
start displacing lower. So, let's just
play out these candles here. When we're
in between ranges like this, like it's
hard to predict. Yeah. [music]
All right, so we're displacing higher.
Again, we have previous day highs a very
obvious draw, so long here. Ooh, nah.
It's like a 3-minute continuation. Bro,
this draw is so obvious. Should I rip a
3-minute? Is this a breakaway gap?
5-minute or 3-minute top? 5-minute?
Yeah. Honestly, I want to try this. Bro,
this is probably going to be a
break-even trade. I want to try this.
I'll go break-even at this high just
because of how obvious this draw is. I
usually need to see at minimum like some
sort of higher time frame, like 5-minute
gap or 15-minute like delivery.
But, this is a 3-minute continuation
that's sponsored from a 15-minute gap
down here. So, if we look down here, we
have a 15-minute leg, then we have a
3-minute, and then just from this
massive amount of displacement in
reaction we're getting with this
1-minute inverse. I'm only going to try
this. Like, this could definitely hit
for the 1:1 just with the amount of
displacement we have. And if this
re-sweeps in the 5-minute boom, I'll get
another entry on it. I'm honestly
willing to try this though. 490 risk,
yeah. Okay, so break-even there. Let's
see.
Let's see if we can get lucky here.
Bang, let's go. 1:1 there. Beautiful.
And this will probably keep going. Keep
rallying up. All right, and we go to the
external high, which I could have held
for the external high, but I like my
piece of the pie, you know. We very
could have well traded down here. Bro,
I'm actually cooking right now. Holy
[\h__\h] But, yeah, it just goes to show
like I'm literally just trading with the
trend. What is the market showing me? We
are displacing higher, so I'm going to
take a long. If we're going lower, I'm
going to take a short. Okay, cool. So, I
mean, we can just play out the rest of
this day. We just rip, right? Beautiful.
All right, don't really care. Let's move
on now. All right, so this is going to
be Thursday. We had a a huge rally up.
Definitely want to be on side that
trend. Probably have this 4-hour sponsor
a move towards this high. That's what
I'm expecting. Also inside this 4-hour
ES. So, let's see. 9:30 open low, high
close here would be beautiful. 9:30 open
low. Give me the open low. Nice. Okay,
we are inside of this 15-minute gap down
here. See if this wants to send this
higher. Nope, we go down in the hourly
or the 4-hour. Okay, so this should be
like low of day. Yeah, now we're
displacing through this, so we are
bearish. So, my bias was just wrong,
which is completely fine. We can now
look for maybe this low down here or
this unfilled 4-hour gap down there.
Damn, just like literally zero entry.
Hopefully Oh my god, generate liquidity.
Oh my god, wait. This actually could be
super textbook. If we literally leave
this low, there's no way, right?
Wait, I don't like this 5-minute gap
though. It's way too discounted, too
many gaps in this range. Go a little bit
higher on Q. Oh, we hit the 50-minute.
We hit the 50-minute. That's actually
perfect, actually. And we swept out the
intermediate high within this, which
makes it good. Higher time frame Q
level. 30-second inverse and trend say
delivery, but we didn't get the
1-minute. I'd rather see a 1-minute
close here. If we get like good
displacement Oh my god, bro. [music]
This is so textbook, actually. Wow. Stop
loss here, TP here. This is probably the
most beautiful trade I've ever seen.
Look at this. 50-minute, we have the
unfilled 4-hour here. Right here, we
just generated that liquidity.
Beautiful.
And this is obviously really discounted,
but a lot of the times, guys, with
continuation models like this, it's
pretty rare you get like a fat rebalance
to EQ of the range, and then you get a
short. Like, that [\h__\h] just genuinely
doesn't happen. Like, you guys see with
like the last trade I took with the
continuation, it was pretty premium.
This trade here, it's pretty discounted.
But, we are having a protected high
here, right? The 5-minute swept out its
internal high. This is a 50-minute
bearish rally gap. There's no reason
price should return back up to this
high. And if we do and we start
generating even more liquidity, then
yeah. But, the reason being like we
already have this generated liquidity
here, it's such a strong draw. The
market is just going to get a little
rebalance and keep dumping. That's what
you want to see with these
continuations. And all this yap, and if
I get stopped out on this, this would
probably be funniest flop, but
>> [laughter]
>> Let's see. We'll do 460 risk. If I get
stopped out after all that, oh no. Oh,
[\h__\h] Oh, no, we good.
Oh my god, break even. This is literally
the most textbook setup so far. Probably
going to dump to this unfilled 50-minute
down here. Watch.
This is going to be like the main draw.
Oh my god, please be him.
Ah.
All right, I was a little bit wrong. It
dumped even farther. But, there we go.
Beautiful. Oh my god, wait. Look at this
profit I could have made. I don't really
care though, I got my 1:1. Could
literally ended the backtesting session
with that if we just held. I'm just
kidding though. Anyways, dude, look at
this profit, bro. We're up 560 risking
1% a trade. Damn, we are actually
cooking right now. We are actually
cooking. I haven't lost a trade yet.
Okay. Cooking, cooking, cooking. Okay.
So, delivery off of this 4-hour gap here
and now we're inside of a new 4-hour
bouncing in between PD arrays. So, when
that happens, I usually like to see what
ES is doing to give us a maybe a clearer
narrative and picture and it is giving
us a clearer narrative and picture being
we are really bearish towards this low
still. I really do like shorts from
here. Really, really do like shorts from
here. Okay. So, let's see.
9:30 giving me the open high. Oh my god,
man. I mean, not like that. Jesus.
Geez Louise. Maybe soup this high. Give
me a short. What even is this level I
have? Nothing yet.
I don't want to see little
bang. 30 second? Ooh. Do we like this 30
second? No, no, no. I mean, everything's
way too choppy right now. I'd like to
see if we can like generate some
liquidity leading up to this 5 minute.
Maybe give me one more sweep. Too choppy
still, man. Can you see it break out of
this range? Holy chop, bro. Look at this
chop fest. And then we have news and now
we have the inverse and I missed it.
But, we inverted this 15 minute no key
level. Ugly chart here. Man, I actually
missed this. We have the 4-hour SMT
here. But, I don't know, man. This is
way too choppy of a chart. I don't
really like this. It hits, but I'm not
going to lie, guys. This is a way, way
too choppy for me. Wow. And then look at
this Oh my god. Look at this 2-minute
inverse back up. Wow. And then we
reverse this whole move back down. Holy
[\h__\h] Wait, this short was actually
really good, guys. I'm not going to lie.
I just missed that. I skipped way too
fast. I skipped way too fast. This short
was actually good. That actually looks
really nice. All right, whatever. We
move on. Don't tell me we are going to
hit this draw on Friday. Don't tell me.
No, we still leave it. Okay. So, like
these daily lows, man, are looking super
juicy. I just wonder when we're going to
go hit them. But, all right. We're
inside this bearish 4-hour. We have a
lot of LRL also stacked up here. Oh my
god. Look at this liquidity, guys. I'm
going to be bearish this whole towards
that. So, give me a short setup, please.
There's also, yeah, a short setup here
will be so textbook. 9:30 open high into
maybe, yeah, just sweeping out this
high. And there's really like no draws
on liquidity like immediate higher,
meaning we should definitely get a
rebalance at this point. Don't give me
that candle, bro. Give me a short entry.
Ooh. Ooh. Okay. No entry, man. I'm going
to have to take some sort of I'll try
this 1-minute the close is pretty trash
and the stop loss is also trash. Like
that's the only place because we have
gaps here. You can probably rebalance,
too. Just this draw in general is so
freaking obvious, man. I wish there was
a 2-minute or 3-minute or something like
where is an easier Damn. This 30-second
at the top though is probably the move.
I could have ripped that. The reason I
like the short so much is because of
this 15-minute equal lows. We have a
15-minute gap here. Also aligning with
all of these stacked lows right here.
The only problem with this I mean, I
could tighten my stop to like this being
like this is like the breaker block
area. Yeah, I could just like have a
looser stop like this. I think I'm
honestly cool with that and have like a
1:1. All right, let's try this. 1:1 here
or let's aim for the 1:1 with this. All
right, and let's try this. Risking
[music] 570 or 695. All right, [\h__\h] it.
Risk cannot be larger. Okay. All right,
so let's try this. Risking 695 makes
695. Just going to break even here I
have to. Hopefully we just get a direct
candle. Hopefully I don't get stopped.
Give me one more. Oh my god. Holy TP.
Holy TP. The way I adjust my TP's like
in my stop like bro, I'm actually
himothy. Holy [\h__\h] I could have had the
stop loss honestly being here seeing
this as a breakaway gap. Maybe max we
retracing this, but like I don't know
9:30 volatility sometimes we could
retrace. Safe stop loss though, I'm
cooking right now, guys. I'm actually
cooking. I'm in flow state. Holy [music]
[\h__\h] Can I lose a trade, dude? A really
good backtesting session to do. Thank
you, chat for giving me this month 2023
of August. Cooking right now. Daily
chart, we did just sweep out a daily
high, previous day high. We are
rejecting off this area and I do really,
really like these draws here for short.
So, I will be 100% looking for shorts.
Let's see. 9:30 give me an open high.
Open high into maybe a 15-minute bearish
gap. This could send price lower being
this hourly high here definitely could
be protected and then this is the
condition that sends us lower. Bro, give
me a 30-second off this. Bro, give me a
30-second off this. I thought I was
going to get a 1-minute. Okay. Or we go
up to this to this high here. Also,
could be could be could be valid. I
don't really care. Oh, I want to take an
early short here. But, we're inside this
2-minute. I honestly want to wait. I
want to see this 2-minute inverse. I'm
going to wait for highest time for me in
this leg. Wait for the 2-minute inverse.
Get a little bit more confirmation, a
little bit worse or straw war, but it'll
be worth it. See no close there and we
sweep out this low. This is going to be
a sweep. Yep, there's the sweep. Okay.
Bias is wrong. Damn, bias is just like
atrociously wrong. Like, my bias is just
so wrong. Okay. Well, super bullish now.
Maybe some sort of rebalance and give me
a long. Damn, they're already was that
rebalance and a long down there. Little
5-minute entry low sweep. We have an
unfilled 15-minute gap. We have an
unfilled 15-minute gap here. Don't like
this. Fail, fail, fail. Oh my god. Wait,
this could be textbook. 3-minute? Holy
textbook. Wait, is this textbook though?
The reason I don't love this is just
because we're so far from this draw.
Like, when we're usually this Oh, no. ES
though is so close. I lied. I do like
this. We are really close to this. ES,
give me that SMT too. And there's that
bullish SMT at the lows. 3-minute
inverse. We have perfect equal highs. ES
is super close to that high. All right,
I'm going to try this. Is this a close?
Like, I don't know if we closed here.
03, yeah. That means we closed, right?
I'm like pretty sure. Okay. Stop loss
will go here and I'll just aim for that
one to one. Or honestly, I want to just
try this and wait until ES takes the
high. I want to try to go for a big RR
here. But, stop loss to the low. Okay,
perfect. Go for 480 risk. All right,
let's try this 3-minute inverse. That's
the close, yeah? Okay. No break even
yet. We didn't hit this high. Okay. Go
break even now and I'm going to hold
until ES takes out the high, bro. I'm
actually him. Hold up. I'm going to
trail my stop low-key to secure that one
to one. That's not even a one to one.
Nah, [\h__\h] a trail stop. I mean, I'll
just do like a little bit of profit.
This should have just hit. Yeah, we
should just hit here.
Oh my god, I'm cooking. Dude, holy [\h__\h]
Actually cooking right now. Beautiful.
Look at this. This is an 11:00 kind of
trade, but why do I like this so much?
Because 10:00 generated liquidity, we
then trade it lower, SMT here, 3-minute
inversion upside. ES has an obvious
draw. [music] Please tell me this is
high of day. Could have held for all the
way up there, but nah. Yeah, and then we
chop around a little bit. Chop fest now
after having this diabolical run up. I'm
going to lean bullish towards this. Just
leaning bullish because of obviously the
massive displacement we've been having.
So, maybe some sort of open low. Let's
see what 9:30 wants to do. [music]
Nothing. Oh, wait. This might be good.
Equal highs. We have We could just see
this as a protected low, right? This is
What time? This is like this is If this
is London lows, yeah, this is London
lows. This 5:00 a.m. lows. Overnight
session trading to this. 15-minute gap
tap here. Get a one-minute inversion
upside. Little paddy swing. Oops, I
didn't mean to click through that next
candle. But, I'm going to try this.
Little paddy swing here. Okay, I'll try
this long. We have a 15-minute gap tap
here. Sweep out of the intermediate low.
We have generated equal highs. Yeah, I
really like this. I'm going to try this.
One to 1.8 RR. I'll just do one con, one
contract here. Risk 455. Okay, cool. Rip
this. Yeah, so I'm just going to be
cautious here. I mean, this could fit
Like the only reason I really, really
like longs here and I'm not too worried
about this LRL down here is just because
this is a protected low or should be a
protected low, right? Discounted little
4-hour in this range, the second 4-hour
here. I'd want to see this hold and have
the gap that got created off this right
here hold. And we also swept out the
intermediate low. So, let's say I'm
wrong and then we just go back down to
London lows and we want to sweep that
out. Okay, I just don't really see a
reason to go back to London lows, but
could be wrong here and this could just
fail. Nope. Nope. Come on, bro. Give me
the Drake. Drake, I'll break even there.
Cooking right now. Look at this bias.
Called that perfectly. Literally called
that bias perfectly. Said bullish up
until here. High day.
Oh my god.
Himothy, bro. And then look at that
close. If I would have closed up there.
All right, we are [\h__\h] cooking. All
right, August 31st. Let's see. We have I
think another week after this and then
we're good. Okay, again, really bullish.
Why we have a daily internal high right
here. We are just obviously displacing
towards You guys just see how I'm like
not overcomplicating my bias whatsoever.
I'm really just like bullish cuz we're
going up and where's the next swing
high? Right there. So, I'm going to be
bullish until then. Boom. It's super,
super simple. So, that being said, let's
see what 9:30 wants to do. 9:30, okay.
Give me a 5-minute pullback and I'll
honestly rip this long. Damn. No. Give
me a good short, low-key. Could this be
a good short? How are you feeling about
this short? Do I like it? Not really. I
think we're just too bullish on the
higher time frame. Like this could
definitely play just because we are
pretty far from this high. It's not like
too much of a magnet, but I'm not really
willing. Yeah, plays. It worked. Little
1-minute long within this. Oh, it's a
30-second. Man. I don't know. This is
too choppy. 1-minute long down here
worked. Too choppy. 5-minute gap here. I
mean, is it good? We did sweep out this
low. There's an SMT here sponsoring that
on the 5-minute. A little like 1-minute
SMT. Really obvious draw, right? We're
just really obviously going to this
daily internal high. I mean, I'll try
this and just break even up here.
I could see this as a protected low.
Yeah, I'll try this and then just break
even here and just try to target that
daily internal high. [\h__\h] it. Let's try
it. All right, I'll go for 1% risk.
Number of contracts, one. Are we going
to do Nah, that's a lot. 730 risk. I'll
do 370 risk. [\h__\h] it. A little bit lower
risk on this. Okay, just quick break
even on this. It'll probably be a break
even trade.
Yeah.
That's why I go break even though.
That's why I go break even because look,
we got super close to this high and then
we never hit it. So, W break even, that
would have cooked me. I'm not going to
be happy with that. And now, maybe a
long. I don't even know if I like this
PA. I don't really like this price
action. No, I'm not going to look at 11.
See, we don't even hit it. Do we hit it
in the next day? The next day we hit it
with a [\h__\h] Drake candle in the
upside. Okay. So, drawing liquidity was
right obviously, but just no entry
towards that. Now, again, I'm just still
going to try to trade with the trend,
although these do look super juicy.
These lows look super juicy. A short
here would be super juicy. Look at this
8:30 low. Wow. Open high. Give me an
open high. Sweep out this high and give
me a short, bro. Keep Sweep out this
high and give me a short. It's 9:23.
Premarket short. Oh my god, this is A+
but it's premarket. No, it's premarket.
This short is so good. Man, I wish I
could have taken something like this.
It's just against my rules to trade
premarket. Bro, I just want to like
[\h__\h] short right now. But, damn. That
was so good. It's literally exactly what
I want to see happen, bro. It was just
against my rules. Okay. Could get a
reaction off this um after sweeping out
all these lows, right? Higher time frame
is obviously super bullish, [music] so
maybe some sort of reaction. This could
be the condition. Could get a little
mech. Is this a mech model? Okay. Going
lower. Sweeping out this low right here.
We still have lows. Honestly, bro, I'm
not really loving anything right now.
Okay. I mean, let's see. All right. We
are holding this for too many gaps
still. Like, what is that close? I don't
know, man. I'd rather short this if I'm
being completely honest. Like, looks
bearish. 30 second here?
No 30 second?
30 second here? Nope. Okay, I could see
this 5 minute for alley gap. 4 minute
inverse. Honestly, I want to try this. 4
minute inverse. We have a sweep on this
15 minute high. Could be a protected
high for sure. We still have lows here.
This is a very bearish move, honestly.
Daily internal high sweep. Yeah, I'm
going to try the short for sure.
4-minute inverse the downside. Highs
time frame in this live is no 5-minute,
right? Okay. So, we'll try the short.
Stop loss here. Let's go for the TP down
here for like a 1:2. This will be a fat
trade if this hits. Okay. Risk, we can
risk 645. That's cool. Again, it's hard
to do like perfect risk. What is going
on? Just give me one phone. Okay, here
we go. So, I think a break even point
could be here. I don't know. I don't see
a point honestly to go break even. So,
anywhere on ES that looks good. Let's
just play it by how the candles are
moving honestly. Let's see. Oh wait, the
close wasn't even there. Where the [\h__\h]
is the close then? Okay, the close is
there. Okay.
I don't understand like sometimes like
these backtests and size a little bit a
little bit glitchy, but maybe I just had
to refresh. Either way, I don't really
see a point of going break even anywhere
honestly, guys. There's no real like
point. I think I'll just like let this
trade run if I'm being honest. Okay, so
some place like this, yeah, now I should
go break even, right? We retraced into
whatever gap this is. This is yeah,
whatever like a 1-minute gap, 2-minute
gap, right? We retraced into this.
Swapped out the internal high here. We
should not go back to this point now,
right? So, this is sometimes what I like
to do is just like let the trade play
out and then go break even. There's not
really like an obvious break even point
sometimes. All right, super close to the
draw here, right? We're also like Look
at all these stacked generated lows
here. I really, really like this.
Hey, man. Like, I don't know
how I'm cooking this how I'm cooking
this hard. I'm not going to lie. But, we
are cooking hard, like very hard. Okay,
holy [\h__\h] bro. I'm not going to lie.
This is like one of the craziest runs
I've had in the past succession in a
while, bro. Holy [\h__\h] This is crazy.
Okay, I'm pretty sure September
this is bank holiday now.
It's Labor Day, I'm pretty sure. Yeah,
this is Labor Day for sure. Look at the
I mean, if you just look take a look at
these candles. Okay, we'll move on to
the next day. Look at the short. Oh,
wow. Missing out on great PA during a
bank holiday. Okay. But, I think this is
last week. So, let's see if we can end
this week. Bro, 100% win rate would
actually be crazy. I have a 70% win
rate, guys, but there's sometimes
obviously where you can have like a 100%
win rate month. Oh, wow, this is really
good for a short. Look at this. Daily
gap here. We're rejecting off the daily
high and MACD model. Oh my god, give me
the short. Yes, probably in the same
spot. Yep. Look at ES's draw. I'm going
to get 84. Oh my god, textbook short.
Textbook short, 9:30 open high, ready?
Open high. Sweep out this high. Give me
the entry. Holy [\h__\h] Is the DAX just
blessing us with trades?
>> Is it though?
>> I'm going to fade this, guys. Damn, I'm
on 10%. Okay, I got to finish this fast.
I'm going to fade this just because of
this. I'm going to fade this just
because of that internal high. There's
no real key level here is the problem,
guys. There's no like gap really to sell
this low, so I'm going to fade this. If
we go up there, I will take a short.
Man, it plays out. It plays out, but
it's this price action's horrible. Yeah,
this PA is actually dog water. I mean,
now I'm not I mean, I'm definitely I
mean, should I take something like this?
Actually looks really solid, I'm not
going to lie. Hourly intermediate high.
We're at 3-minute. I'll wait for the
3-minute close. If we got a 3-minute
close, I will try the short, honestly.
3-minute short, we can try to close.
Wow. I mean, yeah, that's why there's I
mean, there's no no close on that
3-minute. Okay, end of the day there,
and we can move on. Damn, my computer's
going to die. Okay, this is the last
week though, Wednesday. Let's see, let's
see, let's see. Still same draw. I mean,
we're still really choppy in a really
shitty range right now, so either an
open high or just placing lower and we
can get a continuation. Okay, going
lower. No entry whatsoever on anything.
Going up now. Sweeping out something.
Not really anything again, there's no
real key levels I like right now. I
don't like trading within ranges like
this, bro. It's just a lot of chopping
out. Yeah, I mean, your shorts work, but
super rangy. Some sort of 5-minute
continuation here could be great.
5-minute equal highs, perfect. Go up to
that. Go lower now. Okay, 3-minute. I'll
take the 3-minute. Okay, 3-minute
inverse, 5-minute gap. Draw on the
liquidity being this un before. Really
textbook setup. Super textbook. TP would
be down here. Okay, I mean, and again,
textbook setup. We have a 5-minute
intermediate high sweep, 5-minute gap
top. Draw on the liquidity still lower.
ES just probably dumping right now.
Yeah, it's absolutely dumping. So,
definitely trying this short. Okay,
we'll go with sell one and Q 3-minute
inverse. There's no 4-minute There is a
4-minute actually. Oh, I do want to wait
for this 4-minute actually. Let's just
see where the close is. No, yeah, let's
just close out of this. Sorry guys, I
want to wait for the 4-minute close.
Okay.
[\h__\h] the 4-minute just cooked us. Man,
that's brutal. That's why sometimes
waiting for the highest timeframe, man,
sometimes can cook you. But, yeah, I
mean, honestly, I'll try this and just
not rip a break even. I think the draw
is super obvious here. I don't think
I'll get a break even. So, I'll still
rip this, just not going to break even.
And I'm out there. All right, honestly,
damn. Okay, so a setup I was really,
really liking. That's unfortunate that
was like the one loss we took. But, I
mean, still a setup I would take like a
hundred hundred out of a hundred times,
bro. I could have had like a stop super
high, maybe up here. Yeah, maybe I was a
little bit too panicky with the stop.
All right, what percent we on? We're on
9%. All right, got to keep going. Got to
keep moving. But, obviously, the draw
was there. I just like kind of cooked
myself on that entry, I'm not going to
lie. Okay, we'll move on. Damn, we did
take a loss. I wanted to have a hundred
percent win rate. That's brutal. Okay,
whatever. Let's see. Going a little bit
fast here. That also could be the
reason, bro.
Inside of the this big 4-hour computer
is about to computa.
Computa, don't die. Okay, just bearish
as hell, bearish as hell, bearish as
hell. Okay, super bearish here. 9:30
open high. Or an open low. What are we
doing? Go higher. Wait, hold up. I love
longs here. Wait guys, I'm not going to
lie, I'm going to try this long. I don't
know why I like wasn't really paying
attention to this, but I do really like
this for a rebalance. Yeah, the stop
loss is absolutely cooked, but look at
these un Look at this unfill 15-minute.
Like, look at this draw. And look at
like the sheer amount of trendline like
leading up to that uh 4-hour tap. Yeah,
I'm going to try this for one to one.
Bro, give me a 30-second play Yeah,
30-second OB I can put here. This is not
too tight of a stop. I actually do like
this. Okay, I'm going to try this
though. I'm a little late on my entry,
honestly. Should have gotten in on this
one minute little patty swinging
version. All right, we'll rip this one
to one. Let's try it. Come on, bro.
Break even? Just give me a one to one.
That's all I'm asking. Give me one to
one. Banger.
Banger. Let's [\h__\h] go, dude. Look at
that. I mean, it's just an obvious
swing, right? We end up end up going
lower. I still think the draw could be
lower here on ES, right? We do have that
low, but I mean, the generated liquidity
leading up to this is just way too
[music] obvious. Now, we could go lower.
Ooh, edging low, edging the low. Wow,
you really just edged that low. Okay,
cool. Move on to Friday. Okay, so this
will be the last trading day of the
sesh. Some see at the top here. Okay.
Okay. Hold up. Kind of choppy, bro. Five
minute gaps up up here? Maybe a short?
Maybe? Nah. Leaving these lows. We're
not really doing much, that's why I'm
like still willing to maybe take a
setup. Nah. Hold up. Hold up. This is a
setup I should take. Nice. Who's ending
the sesh here? Nah, this two minute
actually looks textbook, though. I'll
try this two minute. I'll try this two
minute. Final trade of the day. Two
minute inverse. I got late entry,
whatever. Highest time frame in this
leg, trading in this two minute gap. Uh,
we have an intermediate low sweeping
that 15 minute. I would go break even at
this unfilled 15 minute. Honestly, bro,
do I like this setup, though? Like, the
problem with this is that ES is just
looking for that protected high. I'll
just break even here. I mean, this is
such a shitty entry, bro. This is going
to be a probably break even trade. But,
I've said that every time and it hasn't
been a break even trade, so let's see. I
mean, I'm just going to go break even at
this terminal high, bro. This is a
pointless trade, bro. Okay, whatever.
Does this even hit? It does hit. What am
I doing? Was that break even shot? Why
did I break even there? I don't know.
I'm fried. I'm just trying to end this.
Okay, guys, well, [\h__\h] what was that?
90% win rate? Let's check the stats
here. Damn, that was actually a really
nice setup. But, it was past 11. It was
on a Friday. I was like, you know,
having that 100% win rate or 90,
whatever percent win rate I'm at right
now, so I wanted to keep it safe. 92%
win rate. Obviously, this isn't my
actual win rate over a large series of
data, over like years of data, my win
rate averages more out to around 70%.
So, this is 92%, but this is really only
1 month of data, right? The month I can
do after this, let's say I do September
like the whole month of September after
this, it could lower down to maybe an
80% then a 70% and like again, that's
just statistics. So, that's really it
but obviously this was a great session.
Um I traded my strategy. I had one loss,
I had around four break evens and 12 Ws.
So, really happy with these stats.
Hopefully you guys learned something
from this if anything, there was a lot
of takeaways that you guys could have
gone from this session. a lot of people
have a lot on how I trade my strategy.
So, hopefully this cleared up some
things for you. If you guys want me to
do another session like this, maybe we
continue and do a little series or
something where I back test a year and
you guys can see my win rate just like
average out because again, not every
month is going to look this good and for
example like the month before this in
March, I had around like an 80% win rate
I think and that's not my actual win
rate, right? I have a win rate of around
70%. So, there's some months where it's
higher, some months where I have like a
50, 60% win rate but again, the average
out of everything is around 70% [music]
for me for my strategy. So, that's what
I want you guys to take away from this.
Don't just see this number right now and
be like, "Oh my god, he's a 90% winner."
cuz it's not accurate. Thank you guys so
much for watching this video though.
Hopefully you enjoyed. If you guys want
me to do any other types of videos like
this, I read comments. I saw a lot of
you guys wanting me to do this back test